const questions = [
    {
        question: "Who won the Ballon d'Or last year?",
        option: ["Messi", "Ronaldo", "Modric", "Rodri"],
        answer: "Rodri"
    },
    {
        question: "Who won the World Cup last year?",
        option: ["Argentina", "France", "Spain", "Netherlands"],
        answer: "Argentina"
    },
    {
        question: "Which country has won the most FIFA World Cups?",
        option: ["Germany", "Brazil", "Italy", "Argentina"],
        answer: "Brazil"
    },
    {
        question: "Which player has scored the most goals in World Cup history?",
        option: ["Pele", "Miroslav Klose", "Ronaldo", "Messi"],
        answer: "Miroslav Klose"
    },
    {
        question: "Which club won the UEFA Champions League in 2023?",
        option: ["Real Madrid", "Manchester City", "Bayern Munich", "Liverpool"],
        answer: "Manchester City"
    },
    {
        question: "Which player has the most international goals?",
        option: ["Messi", "Ronaldo", "Ali Daei", "Neymar"],
        answer: "Ronaldo"
    },
    {
        question: "Which club does Erling Haaland play for?",
        option: ["Manchester United", "Manchester City", "Real Madrid", "Barcelona"],
        answer: "Manchester City"
    },
    {
        question: "Which country hosted the FIFA World Cup 2022?",
        option: ["Russia", "USA", "Qatar", "Germany"],
        answer: "Qatar"
    },
    {
        question: "Who is the all-time top scorer for FC Barcelona?",
        option: ["Luis Su√°rez", "Messi", "Neymar", "Ronaldinho"],
        answer: "Messi"
    },
    {
        question: "Which country won Euro 2020?",
        option: ["Italy", "England", "Portugal", "France"],
        answer: "Italy"
    }
];

export default questions;
